### **AGNIUS ŽUKAS**

Senior Software Engineer

**Mobile:** 236 862 6089

Email: agniuszu@gmail.com

Location: Vancouver, Canada

#### **Profile**

Senior software engineer with a demonstrated 6+ years history of working in different industries. Extensive expertise in large and small system architecture designing and development. Positivity, knowledge sharing, responsibility and lead the way attitude these are the values I strive for every day.

# **Programming Languages**

C#

SQL

**Javascript** 

Go

**Python** 

### **Technical Skills**

.NET core Framework

MS SQL

React.js

**OpenShift** 

MS Business Intelligence tools

### **Experience**

# Senior Software engineer, DANSKE BANK A/S

Mar 2018 -Sep 2020

- Developing REST API's using .NET and .NET core framework;
- Participating in designing new solutions based on business needs:
- Creating Web application based on React.js library;
- Responsible for setting up and managing infrastructure for the new project using Openshift and in house cloud solutions;
- Constantly improving performance and solving various issues on existing solutions;
- Participating in technical interview for finding new teammates

### Software developer, ATEA Ltd.

Oct 2014 -

Mar 2018

- Developing and administering SQL databases;
- Developing web applications in ASP.NET MVC;
- Creating Business Intelligence solutions with Microsoft Business suite;
- Maintaining applications and solving newly arisen problems with a client's help

Software developer - Tester, Jan 2014 - ELGAMA-ELEKTRONIKA Ltd. Oct 2014

- Developing and maintaining testing system (Python);
- Developing and improving software used in manufacture processes (.NET);
- Electricity meters testing;
- Software/Firmware testing

## Wireless hardware testing specialist, WILIBOX Ltd.

Jul 2013 -Jan 2014

- Creating new testing scripts and integrating them into general testing environment (Python);
- Solving problems arisen from customers with faulty hardware:
- Maintaining calibration procedures and modifying/creating calibrations software for new devices;
- Hardware testing;
- Measuring devices characteristics of devices

### **Language Skills**

Lithuanian

English

German

Russian

### **Certifications**

MCSA: SQL Server 2012/2014 - Certified 2018

MCSD: App Builder — Certified 2016;

MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional

MS: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3

**MCSD: Web Applications** 

#### **Education**

BA in Electronics Engineering, 2009-2013 Kauno Technologijos Universitetas

Majored in Intellectual Electronics Systems

Young physicist school "Photon", Siauliai University, Faculty of Technology 2006-2009

### **Personal qualities**

- Quickly and easily master new information;
- Strong skills in communicating with personalities of different perspectives and mindsets;
- Able to work independently as well as in a team;
- A great sense of responsibility;
- Eager to learn new things

#### **Interests**

Enjoy sports, traveling, reading, big history fan